Erin Davis—Front End Web Developer

davisaerin@gmail.com ■ (405)- 585-6448 ■ Oklahoma City, OK 73139 github.com/erin-davis ■ linkedin.com/in/erina-davis

Summary

Front End Web Developer with a focus on accessible web applications, staying current with industry knowledge, and learning new technologies. Experience in data compiling, sales, and customer service has helped develop an exceptional work ethic, skills in communication, and problem solving necessary to succeed in a developer team environment.

Experience With

JavaScript

React

- Angular
- HTML

- CSS/LESS/SASS
- Git/Github

- Yarn/npm
- Jest

Education & Certification

Lambda School

Full Stack Web Developer Course

August 2019 – February 2020

Free Code Camp

Full Stack Developer, Computer Software Engineering

June 2018 – Current

Udemy

The Complete React Developer Course (w/ Hooks and Redux)

Work History

Ecommerce Associate — Extra Cash Pawn August 2019 to Current

- Responsible for online sales
- Research and properly price incoming items to be listed
- Boosted eBay and Amazon sales by over 3 times the amount of the previous month during first month on the job
- Customer correspondence
- Creating and managing large Excel spreadsheets

Cashier — Progressive Parking Solutions Jan. 2017 to August 2019

- Answered questions and provided information about Bricktown and Downtown area.
- Responded to customer requests efficiently and with knowledgeable assistance.
- Processed POS transactions, including checks, cash and credit card purchases or refunds.